Guide to the Walter F. W. Lohnes Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1996-011
  - Courses and degrees (C&D), 1985-86 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Courses and degrees, 1984-85 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) proposal - Contrastive Grammar, 1978-80 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NEH proposal - correspondence and general, June 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NEH proposal - text, June 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NEH proposal - IBA application, June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NEH proposal - appendices, June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Scan data, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - IBG (Institute for Basic German) meeting minutes, 1978-79 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Johansson, Stig (prof?) - correspondence and newsletter of ICAME (International Computer Archive of Modern English) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - IBG - technical (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Institut fur Deutsch Sprache - correspondence and handbook, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - IBG - correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - IBG - correspondence and transcription, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cassidy, Fred (prof. at U. of Wisconsin) - Spoken American English and CALM (Computer Archive of Language Material) correspondence, 1976-79 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CALM retrieval requests (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Akers, Glenn - correspondence and CALM, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - IBG - correspondence and miscellaneous, 1981-83 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - IBG - correspondence and miscellaneous, 1979-81 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NEH grant - final report (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - IBG - correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Seminar on Contrastive Grammar, March 13-15, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Outside requests and correspondence, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - IBG material, 1979-80 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bonn Corpus (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rosengren Corpus (Inger Rosengren) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mannheim Corpus (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Aachen Corpus (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - LIMAS Corpus (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - German - machine-readable databases (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Terminal - correspondence and billing (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IBG and Institut fur Deutsch Sprache - correspondence, 1976-77 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - IBG progress report (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - NEH application (original), April 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NEH application, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NEH - program announcements, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - IBG - computer tapes (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IBG - correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - IBG - agendas, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Pfeffer, J. Alan - "Granddeutsch: Evolution of Basic (Spoken) German," 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Lohnes - "A Corpus-Based Approach to English-German Contrastive Grammar" (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Minutes of IBG meetings, 1979-80 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - IBG Contrastive Grammar Project (proposal, corpora, misc.) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Skip records, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Seminar on Contrastive Grammar - abstracts, March 12-15, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NEH proposal and appendices - "A Corpus-Based Approach to English-German Contrastive Grammar" (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - ? unknown (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Collab. seminar - correspondence and misc., 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gaudiani, Claire L. - leadership project, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Occupation conference, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - STEP program, 1982-84 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and misc., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Language consortium (proposals) and correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lambert proposal, Jan. 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1973-74 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stanford-in-Germany - correspondence, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - IAAL (Int'l. Assoc. of Applied Linguistics - Commission on Language Tests and Testing, 1973-74 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stanford-in-Paris - applications for teaching assignments, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stanford-in-Oxford - applications for teaching assignments, 1984-87 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - (Stanford-in?) Berlin - applications for teaching assignments, 1984-87 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - (Stanford-in?) Florence - applications for teaching assignments, 1984-87 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - (Stanford-in?) Vienna - applications for teaching assignments, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - (Stanford-in?) Tours - applications for teaching assignments, 1984-87 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - GRE - misc., 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - GRE - tests, misc., and correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - GRE test - German language - literary fact, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - GRE test - German language - reading comprehension, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - GRE test - German language - language achievement, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - GRE test - German language - linguistics, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - GRE test - German language - literary sensitivity, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - GRE test - German language - C&C (?) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council - minutes, correspondence, misc., and Stanford New Service (SNS) releases, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council - minutes, corresp., misc., and SNS releases, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council - minutes, corresp., misc., and SNS releases, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council - minutes, corresp., misc., and SNS releases, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council - minutes, corresp., misc., and SNS releases, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council - minutes, corresp., misc., and SNS releases, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council - minutes, corresp., misc., and SNS releases, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - San Mateo/Santa Clara Foreign Language Seminar - misc. and corresp., 1985-86, and California Foreign Language Competency Report, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Stanford-in-Austria class lists, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Modern Language Association (MLA) Cooperative Foreign Language Tests and some corresp., 1975-77 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Study Guide for "German: A Structural Approach," third edition, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Tape script and German language lab exercises (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Assorted material - German articles, corresp., and misc., 1970s (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Notes used in writing tests (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - German Studies - misc. and corresp., 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Studies - info., misc., and some corresp. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Academic Program Committee/Stanford Overseas Studies - info. and corresp., 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Idioms (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Structure (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: "Cloze" (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Applied Linguistics (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Literary Facts (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Quotations (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Missing Part (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Inappropriate Expression (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Culture (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Poetry (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Fiction (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Drama (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - GRE German, 1975 - Items for Review: Non-fiction (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Notes for textbook, misc., 1 photo (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Notes for textbook - units 15-18 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Notes for textbook - units 11-14, master copy (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Notes for textbook - units 8-10, master copy (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Notes for textbook - units 6-7, master copy (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - German Achievement Test Committee, inc. corresp., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Misc. and corresp., 1963-65 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Corresp., notes, and misc., summer of 1964; includes a photo of Stanford-in-Germany (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Graduate Student Teaching - report, minutes, and corresp., 1971-72 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Modern Language Association (MLA) Foreign Language Proficiency Tests - German, URE/GRE, 1969-70 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - GRE - raw material and corresp. with Educational Testing Service (ETS) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - GRE - German (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - GRE - German - corresp. with Educational Testing Service, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Educational Testing Service - corresp. and copy of test, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Corresp. and misc., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Misc. and corresp., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - GRE Items - Linguistics - reference numbers 01-71, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - GRE Items - Literary Facts - reference numbers 101-194, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - GRE Items - Literary Sensitivity - reference numbers 201-282, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - GRE Items - Reading Comprehension - reference numbers 301-399g, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - GRE Items - Culture - reference numbers 401-452, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - GRE Items - Culture and Civilization (C&C) - reference numbers 453-499s, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GRE Items - Language Achievement - reference numbers 501-527, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - GRE misc. test items - reference numbers 528-558, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - GRE Items - Misc. revisions - reference numbers 601-617, Oct. 18, 1971, Committee Review Copy (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - German GRE - misc. notes and revisions (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - German GRE - misc. questions, numbers 3-161 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - German GRE - misc. questions (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Ph.D. requirements - info., notes, and corresp., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Misc., notes, and corresp., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Misc., notes, and corresp., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Misc. and corresp., 1979, 1980, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Haus Mitt - info. and corresp., 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Studies - info., corresp., and misc., 1985, 1986, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Center for European Studies - info. and corresp., 1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Proposal for Center for Central European Studies, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Goethe Institute of San Francisco - corresp., 1988, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Association of Departments of Foreign Languages (ADFL) - corresp. and info., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - American Association of Teachers of German - corresp. and newsletters, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Department of German Studies Newsletter, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - DAAD awards - info. and corresp., 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Department of German Studies - minutes of meeting, corresp., and misc., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Corresp. regarding Die Unterrichtspraxis (UP), 1982-1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 5-year plan for Department of German Studies, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Author Development Program (FAD) - misc. and project proposal in Dec., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - San Mateo/Santa Clara Foreign Language Collaborative Seminar, 1987-88 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - San Mateo/Santa Clara Foreign Language Collaborative Seminar, 1989-93 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Federal legislation (regarding funding for International Studies), 1966-69 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Foreign language placement exams (for Stanford) - corresp. and misc. (actual exam not included), 1980-92 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - German placement test - handouts, 1991-94 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Placement tests - master copy, 1988-90 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Foreign language placement test - statistics (all languages), 1979-80 & 1980-81 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - German language placement test - results and assignments, 1973-81 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Listening Comprehension Committee - corresp. and test, 1968-69 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Listening Comprehension Committee - corresp. and test, 1969-70 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Individual Instruction - misc. and corresp., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Methods regarding Cultures and Civilization (C&C) testing - notes and corresp., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Methods for testing, 1964-? (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Student notes, papers, and misc., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Bad Boll corresp. and newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Institut fur Deutsche Sprache, California Project - info. and newspaper clippings, 1973-74 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "The Foreign Language Requirements: A Collection of Comments," March and April, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - National Center for Education statistics, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - NDEA Stanford summer institute at Bad Boll, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Skytop Meeting, College Entrance Examination Board (CEEB) - papers, 1962-63 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Skytop Meeting, College Entrance Examination Board (CEEB) - corresp. and papers, 1962-63 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - GRE German Committee - corresp. and misc., sample questions and proposals, 1969-70 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - GRE German and French tests - misc., corresp., test evaluations, and tests, 1970-71 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - College Entrance Examination Board (CEEB) and German Achievement Committee - corresp., misc., and test analysis, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - College Entrance Examination Board (CEEB) and GRE Achievement Committee - corresp. and sample tests, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Association of Departments of Foreign Languages (ADFL) - Seminar West at UC Irvine - notes, corresp., info., and misc., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Modern Language Association (MLA) - corresp. and convention notes, 1976-78 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1996-041
  - Inquiries (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Translators Association (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program material (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Background Information (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Washington Trip (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Subcommittee (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Proposals (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Marocchino Proposal, 1986 (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Monterey Institute of International Studies (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Inquiries (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Translation Projects (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Assorted correspondence, 1980's (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1984-86 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Search for Language Center Director, 1995 (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Enrollment figures (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Teaching Fellow Handbook, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Geoffrey Eroe - Dissertation (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - German Studies 31A/131 Distribution Requirement (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Language Requirement (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - German-American School Society of San Francisco (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Western Association for German Studies (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Center for Russian and East European Studies (CREES) Evaluation Committee, 1987 (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Germanisitik in den USA" - Sudwestfunk, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - History of German Dept. at Illinois - James M. McGlathery (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - History of Illinois Department - "German and Scandinavian at Illinois," by James M. McGlathery, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - History of German Dept. - Ohio State - "The History of the Department of German of the Ohio State University," by Oskar Seidlin, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Helmut Rehder - In Memoriam (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - John Van Cleve and Leslie Wilson - Reform of German Studies (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - University of Alberta - Survey (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Helga Schubert - "Judas-frauen" (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Advising, 1986-1992 (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Advising, 1983-1986 (+correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Oral Proficiency Seminar, Sept. 1984 (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ETS (Educational Testing Service) Oral Proficiency Testing Manual, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - PenNEH - University of Pennsylvania with the National Endowment for the Humanities, and foreign language seminar (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann 2nd edition tape scripts, used for recording at Hagens Studio, Princeton, NJ (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann-Petig 4th edition (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann 4th edition - Illustrations (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann 4th edition (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Maureen E. Schumacher - paper on environment (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Translator-Interpreter Committee (TIC) Talks (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reports regarding Translator and Interpreter Program (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Texts (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Texts and articles (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Translator and Interpreter certificates (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - German Chair Application, 1977, 1984 (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Application to Volkswagenwerk-Stiftung, 1978 (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - German Chair Application, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Austrian Chairs, 1985/86 (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Gottfried Scholz - articles and correspondence (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - German activities and reports (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Contact with University of Minnesota, 1980-89 (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Austrian Visiting Professorship (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Peter Gerlich - papers and correspondence (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Krapf - Frodl correspondence (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Austrian chair (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Walter Greinert regarding Austria - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kurt Steiner - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Auslandsoesterreichern in U.S. - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Austrian Chair - correspondence and appointments (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Austrian Chair, German Department Appointment, 1983/84 (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Austrian Studies Chair, Establishment of Committee in Austria (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Austrian Chair, 1982/83 - Streissler, Rothschild, et. al. (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Endowed Austrian Studies Professorship - establishment and agreements (+correspondence) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Texts and articles (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Catherine L. Gaines - "The Translation of Various Chapters From ‘Oesterreich 1985'" (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - James Gardner - Translation of The Concept of the Embryonic Field by Alexander Gurwitsch (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Content and Uses of Dictionaries, Dictionaries for German, and Other Useful Books (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Report to Minister von Schleinitz: Prussian and the Italian War (in envelope sent by M. Reilly (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Certificates - blank (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Translators and Interpreters certificates (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Jacqueline A. Hahn - translation project (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program proposals (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - reports and statistics (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Etilvia Arjona - "Translator and Interpreter Training in Europe and the U.S.A." (rough copy) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - general (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Innovation Fund Proposal (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dolmetsch Program (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Inquiries - jobs (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - correspondence (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Translators and Interpreters Program - Stanford correspondence (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - German 1, autumn 1989/90 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann questionnaire, 1983 (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann 1 - Huffines material (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann - German: A Structural Approach - rough draft (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann - German: A Structural Approach - rough draft (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann - German: A Structural Approach - rough draft (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Illustrations and other materials for Lohnes and Strothmann (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann student guide and complete tape script (pp. 1-120) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Lohnes and Strothmann I - corrections (+correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Illustrations (originals) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - W.W. Norton correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Department of German Studies, 1994-95 - correspondence and miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Department of German Studies, 1993-94 - correspondence and miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Department of German Studies, 1992-93 - correspondence and miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Courses and degrees, 1990-91 (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Teaching assignments (L.D.), 1989-90 (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Courses and degrees and teaching assignments, 1988-89 (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Central European Studies Group (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Tubingen - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - German 103, spring 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lecturer's salaries, 1988 (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - German 1 - 2, attrition information, Feb. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Language Visiting Committee, spring 1992 (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Center for European Studies - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Central Eurpean Studies Center - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for a Center of Central European Studies, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Seminar on Central European Studies (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - German 302 final exams (students'), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - German Conversation 2aB final exams (students'), 1972 (+correspondence) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Department of German Studies, 1991-92 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Department of German Studies, 1990-91 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Department of German Studies, 1989-90 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Department of German Studies, 1988-89 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Department of German Studies, 1987-88 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Department of German Studies, 1985-86 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Department of German Studies, 1984-85 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Language Committee - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hummel Papers (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Ambiguous Objects as Impediments to Interactive Teaching: Direct Objects and Predicate Objects"; and "Sprechereinstellung as a Key to Understanding and Teaching Subjective Modal Verbs" - by Robert D. Hummel (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lohnes' reviews of the papers of David Weible, editor (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Review of CALIS materials for Lohnes, Strothmann, Petig (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Culture notes (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ashliman Exercises (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Review of tape scripts (?) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hummel comments on Lohnes-Strothmann (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 8)